A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, photographs, RG 2, 1958-1990 FA499
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, Program and Policy - Humanities, 911; 0.24 Cubic Feet 1 half-legal document box
  - Veisse, J. (Box 12, Folder 672)
- Administation, Program and Policy - Agriculture, 923; 0.24 Cubic Feet 1 half-legal document box
  - Staff Candidates (Ralston), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 673)
  - Unidentified Material (Box 12, Folder 674)